I was sleeping.
寝てた
Were you sleeping?
寝てた?
dazzling.
眩しい
Did you sleep looking sexy?
セクシーな格好で寝てたの?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
What is this?
なにこれ?
Congratulations, I was asleep.
おめでね、寝てたのに
This is so see-through.
スケスケだよ、これ
Dislike
嫌
is.
だ
Yeah.
うん
It's a string.
紐 じゃん
Yeah, string.
うん、紐
string?
紐?
Can I take this?
取っていいの、これ?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Sleeping, yes.
寝てるよ、そう
One drink, right?
一杯で、そう?
Hey, are you going to pinch me?
ちょっとさ、 挟むの?
Just one drink, yeah.
一杯で、 うん
In between.
挟んで
I won't.
しないよ
real?
ほんと?
Isn't that what you're doing?
してるんじゃないの?
I haven't.
してない
It doesn't come out.
出ない
Did it really come out?
ほ んとに出た?
I can't take it anymore.
もう我慢できない
Yeah.
うん
Looks like it's about to come out.
もう出ちゃいそう
It's fast though.
速いけど
fast.
速い
terrible.
やばい
It's too erotic.
エロすぎで
It was too erotic.
エロすぎた
Was it too erotic?
エロすぎた?
I just let it out.
ちょっと、出しちゃったわ
Did you take it out?
出しちゃったの?
Yeah.
うん
Just put your hands behind me and use your feet.
ちょっとさ、 後ろに手ついて、 足で、
Your left hand.
左手をね
Look.
ほら
It's amazing.
すごいされてる
good night.
おやすみ